

PROFILE

Systems engineer student. Technologist in information systems analysis.

Web developer programmer technician With 2 years of experience working on personal projects, and extensive experience in various fields of work. High sense of belonging and easy adaptability to different environments and people. With strengths in teamwork, leadership and solution to difficulties.

In all the work fields in which I have worked, I have started as the new one and have ended up being one of the most outstanding!

CONTACT

TELEPHONE: 3212376324

WEB PORTFOLIO:

https://wilmerarboleda.tk/

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/wilmerarboleda-b23b411bb/

MAII:

wilmerv0792@gmail.com

self learning Family Entrepreneurship sport

WILMER ARBOLEDA

Frontend Developer

EDUCATION

University of san José (Bogotá)

2021 - 2022

Computer systems análisis technologist

Technical institute System Plus (Tuluá)

2018 - 2020

Web developer technical

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web directory Mi Tuluá, web designer

2020 - 2022

Designer and Administrator of Web page Designer and Administrator of mobile app Links new merchants

Designer of logo and graphic parts

Web directory Mi Roldanillo. Web designer

2020 - 2022

Designer and Administrator of Web page Designer and Administrator of mobile app Links new merchants

Designer of logo and graphic parts

SOME LANGUAGES AND TECHNOLOGIES









